Presence of key acknowledged.
Unlocking special code.
Key?!
Yes.
I'm not from this world.
What?!
I'm a survivor from the ruins.
Look out, Krulcifer!
Fight for the sky
afuredasu kanjou mou tomaranai
I can't stop the overflowing emotions
mune ni idaitai bokura no gensou
The illusions we hold so dear
Just revolution
kienai aza ni obiete ite mo
Fear of the scar that won't disappear
toki ga mujou ni sugiteku dake
Won't stop the ruthless passage of time
susumeyo aru ga mama
Go forth, the way you are
Let's burst up!
ima koso kawaru toki
Now is the time for change
Let's boost up!
kakumei no kane no ne ga
The sound of the bell of revolution
doko made mo hibiite yuku
Resounds far and wide
To be the soldier
mou koko ni wa irarenai
We can't stay here any longer
To be the soldier
kaze wo kitte yuke ikite yuke
Cut through the wind, live your life
hiryuu no gotoku
Like a flying dragon
hajimari ga michiru mama densetsu ni nare
As the beginning draws near, become a legend
tokihanatte yuke tonde yuke
Release yourself, fly ahead
inochi wo tagirasete
Overflow with life
erabareshi mono wo matsu sekai wa owari da New age
The world that waits for a chosen one is over! New age!
m 1062.25 676.375 b 1064.375 676.375 1067.25 676.375 1069.25 676.375 1065.375 690.875 1061.5 705.375 1057.625 719.875 1057.375 720.75 1057.5 722 1057 722.75 1055.625 724.75 1054 726.625 1052.5 728.5 1050.875 726.75 1048.5 725.125 1047.75 723 1044.625 712.875 1041.875 702.5 1037.625 692 1034.75 702 1032.125 712 1029.125 721.75 1028.375 724.25 1026.125 726.25 1024.625 728.5 1022.75 726.375 1020 724.5 1019.25 721.875 1015.625 710.25 1012.625 698.375 1009.25 686.625 1008.375 683.375 1006.625 680.375 1005.125 676.75 1009.5 676.75 1014.25 676.75 1017.75 676.75 1016.125 690.5 1023.25 702.5 1026.25 715.5 1028.625 702.5 1037.125 690.75 1034.125 676.5 1037.125 676.5 1041.625 676.5 1045.375 676.5 1045.375 679.875 1044.75 683.375 1045.5 686.5 1047.875 696.125 1050.75 705.625 1054.25 715.375 1057.125 702.625 1063.625 690.75 1062.25 676.375 m 1149.125 727.125 b 1152.625 722.625 1154.25 701.5 1151.5 697.875 1150.5 696.625 1147.75 695.25 1146.625 695.75 1143.75 697 1139.375 699.125 1139.25 701.25 1138.375 709.5 1138.875 718 1138.875 726.875 1136.375 726.875 1131.75 726.875 1126.875 726.875 1132.25 720.125 1132.125 683.375 1126.25 677.625 1130.25 676.375 1133.875 675.25 1138.25 673.875 1138.25 681.5 1138.25 688.375 1138.25 696 1139.75 695.375 1140.75 695.125 1141.5 694.75 1153.75 688 1160.375 692 1160.875 706 1161.125 712.875 1158.5 720.375 1163.875 727.125 1158.875 727.125 1154.375 727.125 1149.125 727.125 m 847.125 707.125 b 853.625 707.125 858.625 707.125 862.875 707.125 862.125 710.75 861.75 714.25 860.375 717.25 859.125 720.375 857.625 724.375 855 725.75 842.375 732.75 828.25 726.625 825.25 712.625 823.75 705.75 823.875 698.125 825.25 691.25 827.5 680.375 836.25 674.625 847.25 675 857.5 675.125 860.125 678.625 858 691.5 856.625 688.5 855.75 687.125 855.125 685.5 852.25 677.25 844.5 675.5 838.375 681.75 830.375 689.875 830.375 713.75 838.5 721.75 842.125 725.25 849.375 725.75 852 722.5 854.75 719.25 852.625 711.375 847.125 707.125 m 770.125 727.25 b 765.5 727.25 762 727.25 759.75 727.25 764.5 712 769.25 696.625 774.25 681.25 775 679 776.875 677.125 778.25 675 779.875 677 782.25 678.875 783.125 681.25 787.125 691.875 790.625 702.875 794.5 713.625 796.125 718.125 798.125 722.375 800.125 727 795.625 727 790.5 727 784.625 727 790.5 721.875 788.25 715.125 784.75 713 780.875 710.625 773.375 710.625 769.375 713 766.25 714.875 764 721.625 770.125 727.25 m 777.5 687.875 b 777 687.875 776.375 687.875 775.875 687.875 774 694.375 772.25 700.875 770.375 707.75 775.375 707.75 779.25 707.75 783.875 707.75 781.625 700.75 779.625 694.25 777.5 687.875 m 919.25 677.625 b 923.75 676.25 927.375 675.25 932.25 673.75 932.25 679.5 932.25 684.875 932.25 690.25 932.25 699.5 932.125 708.75 932.375 717.875 932.5 720.75 933.875 723.625 934.875 726.875 930.375 726.875 925.25 726.875 920 726.875 926.25 720.875 926.125 682.375 919.25 677.625 m 956.125 718.625 b 959.5 720.875 962.75 724 966.625 725.125 968.375 725.75 972.5 723.25 973.375 721.25 974.125 719.625 972 715.875 970.25 714.25 967.25 711.625 963.25 710.375 960.125 707.875 953.875 702.875 955.125 695.5 962.625 692.875 965.625 691.875 969 691.75 972.125 691.75 978 691.625 981 694.25 979.375 701.5 978.125 699.875 977.625 698.125 976.5 697.625 973.75 696.375 970.75 695.25 967.875 695 966.75 695 964 698.125 964.375 698.75 965.5 701 967.25 703.125 969.25 704.625 972 706.75 975.5 707.875 978.125 710 985 715.5 983.75 724.5 975.25 726.875 970.5 728.25 964.75 728.25 960 727 957.625 726.375 956.375 721.625 954.625 718.75 955.125 718.625 955.625 718.625 956.125 718.625 m 1093 717.625 b 1099.125 721.25 1102.5 724.125 1106.375 725.125 1108.125 725.625 1111.875 722.875 1112.875 720.75 1113.5 719.375 1111.5 715.75 1109.75 714.375 1106.75 711.75 1102.5 710.625 1099.625 708 1097.5 706 1095.25 702.125 1095.875 699.875 1096.5 697.125 1099.625 694.25 1102.5 692.875 1105.125 691.5 1108.75 691.75 1111.875 691.75 1117.25 691.875 1120.375 694.25 1118.625 701.25 1117 699.25 1116.125 697 1114.625 696.375 1112 695.375 1109 695.125 1106.25 695.375 1105.125 695.375 1103.125 698.25 1103.5 699 1104.5 701.125 1106.125 703 1108 704.375 1111.125 706.5 1114.75 707.875 1117.625 710.125 1124.25 715.5 1123.125 724.125 1115.125 726.625 1110.125 728.125 1104.25 728 1099.125 727 1096.875 726.5 1095.5 721.75 1093 717.625 m 890.125 726.875 b 895.125 720.125 895 701.375 889.25 694.75 893.875 696.125 897.75 688.875 901.875 695.25 902 695.375 903.75 694.125 904.75 693.75 907.25 693.125 910 691.875 912.375 692.25 914 692.625 915.375 695.25 916.25 697.125 916.625 697.75 915 699.375 914.25 700.5 912.875 699.375 911.5 698.25 910 697.125 909.5 696.625 908.875 696.25 908.25 695.875 900 700 898.125 720.125 906.25 726.875 900.375 726.875 895.25 726.875 890.125 726.875 m 868.875 727.125 b 874.875 720.875 874.875 700.375 868.625 695.5 872.625 694.375 876.375 693.25 880 692.25 883.5 703.75 877.125 716.125 884.5 727.125 879.375 727.125 874.25 727.125 868.875 727.125 m 1074.25 727 b 1080.375 721.375 1080.375 700.75 1074.375 695.375 1078.125 694.25 1081.625 693.25 1085.625 692.125 1088.75 703.5 1083 715.875 1089.5 727 1085 727 1080 727 1074.25 727 m 944.625 693 b 944 688 943.25 683 943 678 943 677.125 944.625 676 945.5 675 946.625 676.125 948.75 677.125 948.625 678.125 948.5 683.125 947.625 688.125 947.125 693 946.25 693 945.5 693 944.625 693 m 883.125 682.75 b 880.25 684.875 878 687.75 876.875 687.25 875 686.5 872.875 684 872.5 682 872.375 680.875 875.375 678 877.125 678 878.75 678 880.375 680.5 883.125 682.75 m 1081.875 675.625 b 1084.25 678.625 1086.75 680.625 1086.5 682 1086.25 684.125 1083.75 685.75 1082.25 687.625 1080.75 686 1078.25 684.5 1078 682.625 1077.75 681 1079.875 679 1081.875 675.625
We managed to get away safely,
but the path out is completely blocked.
What is this place?
They told me that I was found,
as a baby, in a box like this.
You mean...
So does House Einfolk...
Back when my foster father was investigating the ruin in the Ymir Theocracy,
he found me and took me in.
As a piece of the puzzle that is
the ruins and the lost past,
he thought I could be useful.
With no memory of my past,
I lived in House Einfolk none the wiser.
I realized at a very early age that I was adopted.
My parents, my siblings, the servants...
They all treated me like an outsider.
So I worked hard.
In my studies, in etiquette,
in being a Drag-Knight...
So that people would like me.
So that I'd be accepted as part of the family.
But I never got what I wanted most.
I had become skilled enough to receive a Divine Raiment Machine Dragon,
but that only alienated me
from my siblings even further.
I overheard them say that I really must not be entirely human.
The reason I was so bent on exploring the ruins
was that I didn't want to believe it.
I wanted to believe there was
some kind of misunderstanding
and that I was in fact a true
daughter of House Einfolk.
But I guess I truly am a survivor of the ruins.
There's no doubt now that I've seen the ruin react to me.
But I still don't know anything about my past
or whether there are others like me.
B-But it's not like everything here's been
explored, and there are other ruins out—
I'm not exploring any more.
What?
I'm too afraid to go any further.
What if I kept exploring the ruins and still never found others like me, or anyone who'd accept me?
Krulcifer...
I'm sorry you had to listen to all that.
And from a nobody like me.
You're not nobody!
The Ymir Theocracy and the
House of Einfolk don't matter here!
You're our fellow student and Drag-Knight,
and my girlf—my partner!
So please don't...
Please don't say things like that.
Lux, let me give you a fair warning.
You shouldn't always believe
a woman's sad stories.
Was all that a lie?!
Your only weakness is your
excessive kindness to others.
I wanted to see what you'd do,
but this reaction was more than I was expecting.
But really, how can be you so softhearted?
You were a prince of that notorious old empire.
That might be my fate.
I was banished from the imperial court, along with my mother and Airi, on account of my grandfather.
He was a teacher for the imperial family.
But seeing the empire's ways,
I guess he couldn't stay silent.
However...
Please someone help!
My mother!
No one would lend a hand to members of the imperial family they'd suffered under for so long.
In the end, we were shunned and forsaken
by both the imperial family and the people.
What a horrible story.
Didn't you resent them all?
I did.
I believed there wasn't a person in the world who'd stand by us.
I was about to give into hatred.
But...
Philuffy saved me.
She came to see me every day,
even though I had nothing to give her.
So it was her.
That's when I realized that I didn't really want to hate anyone.
The people I cared for...
People I could come to care for...
I didn't want to hate them
because of the empire.
I wanted to create a kingdom where one didn't have to hate the people they love.
If you had become a prince of the new kingdom,
perhaps you could have saved me too.
What?!
A-A drill?!
What do you think, Lux?
This guy's pretty useful, don't you think?
U-Um, I guess so.
By the way, I hope you didn't do anything to Krulcifer.
Anything like what?
A-Are you going to make me say it?! You dunce!
Y-You lecher!
What?!
How am I a lecher?!
You just are—
So in the end, you couldn't
find anything about the key.
And you completely destroyed your Wyvern too.
I said I was sorry.
I'm mad at you for not learning from your past mistakes.
You knew the ruins were dangerous,
and you still acted recklessly.
I'm ashamed of myself.
So the horn wasn't the key.
No. I held it out while inside, but there was no reaction.
Did anything else out of the ordinary happen?
Not really.
I see.
It's a pity that we made no progress,
but we have to play the hand we're dealt.
All right, Lux, drink this.
What is it?
Herbal tea. A present for you from Krulcifer.
It eases fatigue and helps you sleep better.
But...
You'll still make it to the duel.
You should get some rest before then.
Okay. Thanks.
Are you satisfied now, Krulcifer?
Yes. Thank you.
It would be wrong to drag your brother any further into my personal problems.
His job will be over tomorrow.
You still don't understand
anything about my brother.
I see you are punctual, my future wife.
But where is the little boy?
I sent him home.
Is that a problem for you?
Very well.
I assume you're prepared for this.
Yes.
I'm prepared for the worst, as I always am.
Planning to face Lord Balzeride and me by yourself?
You underestimate us greatly.
Miss Alterize.
You can take a nap.
What are you—
Alterize!
All right, let's get this duel underway.
Wise Blood.
Fafnir's ability to see the future, huh?
Splendid.
Then you must know what I'll do next.
What's wrong?
Where are you aiming?
Please refrain from
touching me unceremoniously!
Do you really think you can defeat me?
I can't hit him.
Why is my foresight malfunctioning again?
Because you did not realize
the extent of my true power!
Oh, sorry about that.
That belly will soon carry my children.
I should be a bit more gentle with it.
Do you still plant to fight?
Don't disappoint me by being
ungraceful in defeat.
Disappoint you?
I can see that you're happy.
Happy that things turned out
the way you planned.
You joined the expedition to the ruin in order to see Fafnir's Divine Raiment in action.
The thieves who attacked me before that
were probably your doing as well.
It allowed you to observe Fafnir's ability without getting involved personally.
And I assume it was Azi Dahaka's ability that rendered Alterize unconscious?
Yes. It's just as you say.
I arranged it all...
in order to get my hands on you, the key.
You may know the truth,
but that won't do you any good.
You are a mere tool in this world,
and nothing you do can change that fact.
A mere tool such as yourself
cannot stand against someone like me.
You know there's no one in this world
who would help you.
So accept your fate and
serve me as your master.
Who dares interfere?!
Why?
I'm sorry I'm late.
I, Lux Arcadia, hereby enter this battle.
A pitch-black Divine Raiment Machine Dragon?
I was sure you had run away.
But revealing your identity
to save some woman...
You're more foolish than
I had imagined, Black Hero.
You don't understand anything about her worth!
I won't let you have her.
Then I'll have you tell me all about her worth
after I strike you down!
Reload on Fire.
Stop!
I didn't want to involve you any further!
So why...
Lux!
Completely unflustered even after your
glorious Divine Raiment was countered?
So that's your secret.
What was that, fallen prince?
Are you looking to excuse
your inevitable defeat?
You used Fafnir's Divine Raiment,
Wise Blood, to predict my moves, correct?
Azi Dahaka can steal another's Divine Raiment.
And in order to use that power continually,
you drained Machine Dragon
energy from Krulcifer.
I see. That's what happened to Alterize too.
You steal the abilities and energy of Machine Dragons you touch.
That's what your Divine Raiment does.
I applaud you for figuring that out.
However...
You fell for it, Black Hero!
Reload on Fire.
What's the matter?
Is this what the Black Hero amounts to
without his Divine Raiment?
Why?
Why are you fighting for me? I'm no one to you.
There's nothing for you to gain from this.
That's the best and the worst thing about Lux.
You...
Apparently, Lux saw through our plan.
There's no point in trying to stop him.
He's fighting for you.
Watch Lux as he struggles on for you,
and don't turn away.
Lux Arcadia, you know about
the Ragnarok, don't you?
I intend to fight it for the
sake of this new kingdom.
To that end, I must dig up new weapons and technology from the ruins as soon as possible.
This kingdom can be saved using a single woman from a foreign land.
Don't you think it's a small price to pay?
Or do you want to be responsible for
another crisis in this land, Black Hero?!
Are you losing control?
So that's what your skills amount to.
You can stop now, Lux.
You've done more than enough
to fulfill your job as my boyfriend.
It's not over!
You don't have to go that far!
I was using you.
To me, you're just another tool.
So think of me the same way—as just another tool.
I wish you had done so from the start.
Then I would never have gotten my hopes up.
I would never have felt this pain.
You're my girlfriend.
So I'll save you.
Let me fight.
For you, someone precious to me!
You fool!
I've stolen your Divine Raiment and you're losing control of your Machine Dragon.
What more can you possibly do in that state?!
Recoil Burst!
Die, you hero-wannabe fallen prince!
I don't want to be a hero.
But...
What?!
Since the day I swore to bring down the empire,
I've resolved to fight!
How?!
What happened?
I thought Lux couldn't use his Divine Raiment.
That's not a Divine Raiment.
It's a double-edged sword, where you intentionally allow your Machine Dragon to go out of control,
to focus built-up energy into a single blast.
It's a secret technique Lux came up with
while seeking extraordinary power.
Relying on his skill to pull that off...
That's madness.
Yes, that's how my brother always is.
Not knowing how much I worry for him,
he's always out there fighting for someone.
The duel is over.
Let's go back to our school.
Okay.
If you're so worried about it,
you could've just gone inside.
N-Nonsense! I just came to guard Lux
while he meets with that butler!
What?!
E-Engagement?! I mean...
Don't worry.
With your skills as a Drag-Knight
along with the wisdom you showed
seeing through Lord Balzeride's plot,
I'm certain that Earl Einfolk will
deem you worthy of this marriage.
No, I mean...
I take full responsibility for the incident.
Allow me to make up for that by giving
your relationship my complete support.
But...
I bid you good day, my lady.
Hey, wait!
Hear me out!
Why don't you take a seat?
You're causing a scene.
Y-You're right.
Wait, that's not important now!
We were supposed to be pretending.
How did it come to this?
Oh, but didn't you say so
yourself during the duel?
I'm your girlfriend.
You were pretty firm about it.
I just said that in the heat of the moment.
If you're serious about it,
I have no problem with this engagement.
Don't tease me like that!
Well, I suppose indecisive men
are not really my type anyway.
I came to realize that after
dating you for a week.
I-I see.
But the true you is actually rather bold.
When you show that side of you...
I find you irresistible.
Not enough?
No... It was...
Then, let's keep going.
Miss Lisha?!
If you become my fiancé,
we can go even further.
Um... I... Uh...
What the hell are you two doing?!
kusaki mo nemuru yoru no sumi de sekai no fushi de
In the nook of night where even trees sleep, in a cranny of the world
neiki ni sotto mimi wo tatete hitomi wo tojiru
I hear the breath of someone asleep nearby,
close my eyes, and prick up my ears
kubisuji ni futto atatakana inochi no tsubu ga
A warm seed of life near my neck
koko ni iru tte sakenderun da koe naki koe de
is screaming that it's there, in a voice without voice
umarekawaretara owarinaki you ni
If we can be reborn endlessly
kimi ga nodo wo itamenakute
Let's take such forms
sumu you na sugata ni narou
that we won't need to scream so hard to be heard
sashiatatte futari tabi doko made arukeru
Now we're traveling, the two of us. How far can we go?
ikeru toko made ikou hohaba awasete
Let's go as far as we can, matching each other's pace
tsukiatatte futari tabi koko made kureba
And when we finally get to the end of the path, the two of us
kigi ni natte tachitsukusou
Let's become trees and stay there
raise ni natte mo zutto koko de nemurou
Even in the next world, let's keep sleeping there
futari nemurou towa ni
The two of us, let's sleep for eternity